<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MobileAssignment</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_logout">Logout</string>

    <string name="splash_screen_info">Designed By: \n Khai Wen, Kok Wei</string>
    <string name="register_page_password_hint"> Password \t\t\t\t (Hint: abcD@12345)</string>
    <string name="inquiries">For any inquiry, please call 03-32551678 to our customer services.Or you can email to us lingolearn@gmail.com </string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="InfoSmartPen">\nThe Smart Dictionary Pen is a cutting-edge language learning and translation device designed to revolutionize the way we interact with languages and expand our linguistic horizons. </string>
    <string name="InfoDetailSmartPen">\n1. With the Smart Dictionary Pen, you can effortlessly access the definitions and explanations of words and phrases in multiple languages. Simply point the pen at a word or phrase, and it will instantly display the relevant information on its screen.\n
    \n2. Whether you are a traveler trying to decipher a foreign language menu or a language enthusiast looking to broaden your horizons, the Smart Dictionary Pen has you covered. It provides quick and accurate translations for words or entire sentences, making communication in different languages a breeze.\n
    \n3. The Smart Dictionary Pen enables users to build and save a personal vocabulary list. This feature allows you to keep track of the words you've looked up, making it an excellent tool for language learners aiming to expand their lexicon.\n
    \nIt has many features, the price is also very cheap, you are still waiting for what, come and buy it!!！</string>
    <string name="InfoQB">\nThe ultimate quiz book for family and friends - perfect for home entertainment and virtual pub quizzes.</string>
    <string name="InfoDetailQB">\nPut your general knowledge to the test, and impress your family and friends with your astonishing brainpower and trivia genius.\n\n

    An addictive quiz book for all the family featuring 10,000 questions, The Big Quiz Book has something for everyone. With 10 different general knowledge categories - from Science & Technology, Art & Literature, and Natural History, to Food & Drink, Film & TV, and Sport & Leisure - and three increasing levels of difficulty, it offers a fresh and up-to-the-minute quizzing experience that will educate and entertain all the family.\n\n

    Bursting with fascinating facts to boost your trivia knowledge, whatever your specialist subject or your nemesis topic, The Big Quiz Book is perfect for home entertainment and virtual pub quizzes. You won't be able to put it down!\n\n</string>

</resources>